Guide to the Eugene O'Neill Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1889-1968; Series V; 7.6; (20 boxes)
  - EUGENE O'NEILL
    - Sitting on deck chair at Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.) with Blemie on his lap (7 versions), [1933] (Box 109, Folder 1896)
    - Wolf Lake (N.Y.)
      - Wearing bathing suit, sitting on diving board (2 versions), [1933 or 1934] (Box 109, Folder 1897)
      - Wearing bathing suit, standing on diving board, [1933 or 1934]
      - Wearing bathing suit, about to dive from diving board, [1933 or 1934]
      - Standing on path near a building (2 versions), [1933 or 1934] (Box 109, Folder 1898)
      - Standing next to unidentified man (2 versions), [1933 or 1934]
      - Leaning against fence (copy), [1933 or 1934], n.d.
      - Standing near canoes (copy), [1933 or 1934]
      - Standing on path near woods, [1933 or 1934]
      - Standing near cabin, [1933 or 1934]
      - Sitting in canoe, [1933 or 1934]
        See also: Green "Daily Reminder" 1934, box 84, folder 1502
    - Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Sitting on deck chair, [1934] (Box 109, Folder 1899)
      - Reclining in deck chair, [1934]
      - Standing on lawn, 1934
      - Standing on walkway, [1934]
      - Crouching on beach, [1934]
      - Sitting on dunes, 1934
      - Standing on beach, [1934]
      - Standing with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill on lawn, [1934]
        See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1934, box 84, folder 1502
      - Sitting outside at table with George Jean Nathan (2 versions), [1934] (Box 109, Folder 1900)
      - Sitting on deck chairs outside with George Jean Nathan (2 versions), [1934]
      - Standing outside with George Jean Nathan (2 versions), [1934]
      - Crouching with chicken, "Marcia," on lawn, 1935 (Box 109, Folder 1901)
      - Standing next to chicken, "Marcia," on lawn, [1935]
    - Portraits by Carl Van Vechten at Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Wearing striped robe, sitting on deck chair, close-up, 1936 May 15 (Box 110, Folder 1902)
      - Wearing striped robe, sitting on deck chair, further away, 1936 May 15
      - Wearing striped sport shirt (7 versions), 1936 May 16 (Box 110, Folder 1903)
      - Wearing striped sport shirt and striped robe (7 versions), 1936 May 16 (Box 110, Folder 1904)
        Three inscribed by EO to CMO.
      - Wearing striped sport shirt, standing with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, close-up, 1936 May 16 (Box 110, Folder 1905)
      - Wearing striped sport shirt, standing with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, further away, 1936 May 16
      - Sitting on beach smoking, 1936 May 16 (Box 110, Folder 1906)
      - Sitting on beach holding cigarette, 1936 May 16
      - With Lawrence Langner sitting on beach, 1936 May 16 (Box 110, Folder 1907)
      - With Lawrence Langner standing on lawn, 1936 May 16
      - Group sitting on beach: Lawrence Langner, Fania Marinoff Van Vechten, Eugene O'Neill, Armina Marshall, [1936 May 16] (Box 110, Folder 1908)
    - Seattle (Wash.)
      - Sitting (6 versions), [1936 Nov] (Box 110, Folder 1909)
      - Sitting with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, [1936 Nov] (Box 110, Folder 1910)
      - Leaning on elbow (dark background), [1936 Nov] (Box 110, Folder 1911)
        One print inscribed by EO "To
        [George?]."
      - Head only, [1936 Nov] (Box 110, Folder 1912)
    - Lafayette (Calif.)
      - Standing next to bird bath on lawn, 1937 Jul (Box 110, Folder 1913)
      - Sitting on chair on lawn, 1937 Jul
        Both inscribed by EO to CMO, 1937.
    - Tao House (Danville, Calif.)
      - Standing outside, looking toward camera (copies) (4 versions), 1939 (Box 110, Folder 1914)
      - Standing outside, looking toward fields (copy), [1939]
      - Standing on porch, looking toward fields (copies) (2 versions), [1939]
      - Standing outside, with view of eves of house (copy), [1939] (Box 110, Folder 1915)
      - Standing outside with [Herbert Freeman?], [1939] (Box 110, Folder 1916)
      - Standing with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill and black cat in front of valley, 1939 (Box 110, Folder 1917)
        Taken by Fania Marinoff Van
        Vechten.
      - Opening up piano, "Rosie", [1939] (Box 110, Folder 1918)
      - Playing piano, "Rosie," looking up, [1939]
      - Playing piano, "Rosie," with eyes closed (2 prints), [1939]
        One print of third photograph
        inscribed by EO to CMO, 1939 Feb.
      - Leaning against piano, "Rosie" (copy), [1939], n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1919)
      - Close-up, in front of lamp (2 versions), [1939]
      - Sitting on window sill, [1939]
      - Standing in front of cabinet, smoking (copies) (2 versions), [1939] (Box 110, Folder 1920)
    - Portraits by Horace Bristol from Life magazine
      - Sitting at desk at Tao House (Danville, Calif.), close-up, 1939
        Inscribed by EO to CMO, 1940 Feb.
      - Close-up, head only, 1939
      - Sitting with Blemie on patio (3 versions), [1939] (Box 110, Folder 1921)
    - Tao House (Danville, Calif.)
      - Sitting in yard (3 versions), 1941 Jun (Box 110, Folder 1922)
      - Standing near side of house (2 versions), [1941 Jun]
      - Wearing bathing suit, standing in garden with Oona Chaplin wearing bathing suit (3 versions), [1941 Jul] (Box 110, Folder 1923)
      - Sitting with Oona Chaplin at table outside (3 versions), [1941 Jul] (Box 110, Folder 1924)
      - On ladder, tacking up jasmine (8 versions), 1941 Aug 4 (Box 110, Folder 1925)
        For other prints of versions 5 and
        8, see also: Tao House Album #3,
        box 115, folder 2123
      - Standing near pool (2 versions), 1941 (Box 110, Folder 1926)
      - Sitting on stump near pool (2 versions), [1941]
        See also: Green "Daily Reminder" 1942, box 36, folder 1510
      - Sitting on chair near pool, [1941]
        See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1942, box 36, folder 1510
      - Sitting at table outside, eating (8 versions), [1941] (Box 110, Folder 1927)
      - Sitting on patio (copy), [1941], n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1928)
      - Sitting on patio steps, [1941?] (Box 110, Folder 1929)
      - Standing on patio, [1941?]
      - Sitting in garden (2 versions), [1941?]
    - Portraits by Life magazine at Tao House (Danville, Calif.)
      - Sitting at desk, 1943 (Box 110, Folder 1930)
      - Standing next to ship models, 1943
      - With piano, "Rosie", 1943
      - With collection of record albums, 1943
      - Sitting with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill in living room, 1943
      - Crouching next to tree in garden, 1943 (Box 110, Folder 1931)
      - Standing in walkway, looking up at tree in garden, 1943
      - Sitting in garden, 1943
      - Sitting with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill in garden, 1943
      - Standing at railing, smoking, 1943
      - Standing at railing, looking toward fields, 1943
    - Standing in yard at Tao House (Danville, Calif.) with Herbert Freeman wearing military uniform (6 versions), [1944?] (Box 110, Folder 1932)
    - Photograph of drawing by Mai-Mai Sze of Eugene O'Neill (copy), 1945, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1933)
    - Portraits by F. Roy Kemp at 35 East 84th Street, New York
      - Contact prints (5 pages), 1946 Aug 15 (Box 110, Folder 1934)
        With note of explanation by CMO.
      - Sitting inside (4 versions, 5 prints), 1946 Aug 15 (Box 110, Folder 1935)
        One print (fragment) of first
        version inscribed by EO to CMO,
        1946 Dec. One print of first
        version matted and signed by
        Kemp.
        folder 2547
      - Sitting outside (10 versions), 1946 Aug 15 (Box 110, Folder 1936)
      - Standing on balcony (4 versions), 1946 Aug 15 (Box 110, Folder 1937)
        matted and signed by Kemp.
        folder 2548
    - Portraits (8 versions) in New York, [1946] (Box 110, Folder 1938)
    - Sitting with Carlotta Monterey O'Neill at rehearsal for The Iceman Cometh (copy), [1946], n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1939)
    - Group picture at dinner for Robert Edmond Jones at Coffee House Club, 1947 Dec 18
      With letter of explanation from Jo
      Mielziner to CMO, 1955 Feb 18.
    - Marblehead Neck (Mass.)
      - Standing on lawn at front of house, [1948?] (Box 110, Folder 1940)
      - Standing on lawn near ocean (2 versions), [1948?]
      - Standing on lawn at front of house, [1948?] (Box 110, Folder 1941)
      - Standing in driveway at side of house, [1948?]
    - Portrait, close-up, from Minnesota Theatre Company (copy), [194-], n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1942)
  - CARLOTTA MONTEREY O'NEILL
    - Sitting on bench, next to dog on table, [189-] (Box 111, Folder 1943)
    - Debut portrait by Lallie Charles in London, 1909 (Box 111, Folder 1944)
    - Sark Island (England)
      - Sitting outside, surrounded by four unidentified women and one unidentified man standing, 1909 (Box 111, Folder 1945)
      - Swimming, with unidentified woman, 1909 (Box 111, Folder 1946)
    - Dressed as Luana in The Bird of Paradise, [1915] (Box 111, Folder 1947)
    - Standing outside, wearing black dress and scarf, 1917 (Box 111, Folder 1948)
    - Sitting on park bench, [191-] (Box 111, Folder 1949)
    - Leaning over railing of boardwalk at beach, wearing coat trimmed with fur, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 1950)
    - Portraits by Marcia Stein
      - Looking toward camera, 1922
        See: Portfolio of fourteen portraits by Maurice Goldberg, box 144, folder 2556
      - In The Hairy Ape, sitting, [1922] (Box 111, Folder 1951)
      - In The Hairy Ape, close-up, 1922
    - California
      - Sitting on hammock outside, next to Cynthia Chapman Stram, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 1952)
      - Standing outside, with arms around Cynthia Chapman Stram, [1922] (Box 111, Folder 1953)
      - Sitting on bench next to Cynthia Chapman Stram (2 versions), [1922]
      - Standing outside with Cynthia Chapman Stram, [1922]
    - Photograph by Peter A. Juley & Son of painting by Abram Poole of Carlotta Monterey O'Neill as Mlle. Clarion in Voltaire in 1922 (copy), n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1954)
    - Sitting on stool, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 1955)
    - Portraits by Nickolas Muray
      - Wearing bridal outfit, front view, [1924] (Box 111, Folder 1956)
      - Wearing bridal outfit, side view, close-up, 1924
      - Wearing bridal outfit, side view, far away, 1924
      - Wearing long dress, with back to camera, 1924
    - Wearing black dress, standing next to ivy-covered wall, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1957)
    - Portraits by [Demeyer?]
      - Wearing black dress, sitting back in chair, [192-]
      - Wearing black dress, leaning forward in chair, [192-]
      - Wearing black dress, leaning forward in chair, close-up, [192-]
      - Wearing black dress, showing silhouette against wall, [192-]
        Third photograph inscribed by CMO
        to Carl Van Vechten and Fania
        Marinoff Van Vechten, 1930.
      - Wearing white dress, sitting back in chair, [192-]
    - Portfolio of fourteen portraits by Maurice Goldberg, [192-]
      For list of contents, see: Appendix
    - Portrait by Ira L. Hill's Studio, wearing fur-trimmed cape, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1958)
    - Portraits by Nickolas Muray
      - Wearing Asian robe, close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1959)
      - Wearing black dress trimmed in lace, close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1960)
      - Wearing velvet cape, close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1961)
      - Wearing long lace dress, with velvet bow, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1962)
    - Portrait by Sarony, N.Y., wearing white dress, trimmed with fur, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1963)
    - Portraits by Marcia Stein
      - Looking left, close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1964)
      - Looking right, close-up, [192-]
      - Wearing black velvet dress, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1965)
      - Wearing sheer, dotted dress, close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1966)
    - Portrait by Jean de Strelecki [in production?], lying near candle and picture of madonna and child, [192-]
    - Portrait by White, wearing black dress, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1967)
    - Studio portrait, wearing white jacket and blouse (2 versions), close-up, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1968)
    - Standing in park with hand on hip, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1969)
    - Photograph of drawing by Ralph Barton of Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, [192-] (Box 111, Folder 1970)
      Mounted on card and signed:
      "Greetings! Carlotta Monterey."
    - Portrait by Albin, wearing shawl, 1925
      Inscribed by Albin to CMO, 1925.
    - Belgrade Lakes (Me.)
      - Wearing bathing suit standing next to lake, [1926 summer] (Box 111, Folder 1971)
      - Sitting on steps of house holding white dog, [1926 summer]
      - Standing outside, wearing hat, 1926 Jul (Box 111, Folder 1972)
    - Portraits by Nickolas Muray
      - Wearing hat, close-up, [1926] (Box 111, Folder 1973)
      - With hair pinned on side, close-up, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 1974)
        Inscribed by CMO to EO, 1926.
        Annotated on back by CMO.
      - With short hair, side view, close-up, 1927 (Box 111, Folder 1975)
    - Studio portrait by Ben Pinchot, wearing flower, close-up (3 versions), 1927 (Box 111, Folder 1976)
    - Photograph by Peter A. Juley & Son of painting by Giulio de Blois, 1927
      Photograph signed "Giulio de Blois,
      N.Y. 1927."
    - Passport, 1927 Feb 24 (Box 111, Folder 1977)
      With explanatory note.
    - Studio portrait for passport, [1927 Feb 24] (Box 111, Folder 1978)
    - Baden-Baden (Germany)
      - Standing in front of fence (2 versions), [1927 Jul]
        See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1928, box 83, folder 1496
      - Standing in front of fence with Olga van Henkelow, 1927 [Jul]
      - Standing in front of fence with Olga van Henkelom and her husband, 1927 [Jul] (Box 111, Folder 1979)
      - Wearing suit, carrying walking stick, two contact sheets (five prints), 1927 Jul (Box 111, Folder 1980)
    - Guéthary (France)
      - Standing next to stone railing, looking at sky, 1928 Apr (Box 111, Folder 1981)
      - Sitting on deck chair, [1928 Apr]
      - Wearing shorts sitting on beach, 1928 (Box 111, Folder 1982)
        Inscribed by CMO to EO, 1928.
      - Standing in front of car, [1928] (Box 111, Folder 1983)
      - Standing next to metal railing, [1928] (Box 111, Folder 1984)
      - Sitting, smoking, [1928]
    - Studio portrait in Biarritz (France), [1928] (Box 111, Folder 1985)
    - Standing at railing on boat to China, [1928 Oct] (Box 111, Folder 1986)
    - Passport, 1929 Mar 14 (Box 111, Folder 1987)
    - Studio portrait for passport, [1929 Mar 14] (Box 111, Folder 1988)
    - Cap-d'Ail (France)
      - Leaning against stone wall, wearing brimmed hat, 1929 (Box 111, Folder 1989)
      - Standing on hillside, wearing cloche hat, [1929]
      - Sitting on steps, wearing cloche hat, [1929]
      - Sitting on porch, leaning on elbow (fragment), [1929] (Box 111, Folder 1990)
    - Studio portrait, close-up, 1929 (Box 111, Folder 1991)
    - Château du Plessis (St. Antoine-du- Rocher, Indre et Loire, France)
      - Sitting on wire chair in front of steps, [1930] (Box 111, Folder 1992)
      - Standing in road, [1930]
      - Standing in front of house, [1930]
        For another version of first
      - Standing in field, close-up (2 versions), [1930]
      - Standing in field, far away, [1930]
      - Sitting with unidentified woman on park bench, [1930]
      - Standing next to pool, [1930]
      - Standing with Blemie near pool (2 versions), [1930] (Box 111, Folder 1993)
      - Sitting next to pool, [1930]
        For other prints, see also: Château
        du Plessis album #1, box 114,
        folder 2119
      - Sitting next to pool with Blemie (2 versions), [1930]
      - Sitting next to pool, with parasol, 1930 (Box 111, Folder 1994)
      - Standing with Lillian Gish and George Jean Nathan, [1930]
    - Studio portrait for identity cards, [1930 Feb 4] (Box 111, Folder 1995)
    - Touring Club de France card, 1930 Feb 26 (Box 111, Folder 1996)
    - Carte d'identité, 1930 Mar 31 (Box 111, Folder 1997)
    - Standing in archway in Granada (Spain), [1930] (Box 111, Folder 1998)
    - Seville (Spain)
      - Standing on balcony next to shutters (2 versions), [1930] (Box 111, Folder 1999)
      - Standing on balcony next to metal railing (2 versions), [1930]
    - Spain
      - Standing on balcony with towers in background, [1930] (Box 111, Folder 2000)
      - Sitting on stone balcony, [1930]
    - Leaning against balcony in Las Palmas (Canary Islands) (2 versions), [1931 Mar] (Box 111, Folder 2001)
    - Passport, 1931 Apr 9 (Box 111, Folder 2002)
    - Sitting on lawn of Beacon Farm (Northport, N.Y.) next to Blemie standing, [1931 summer] (Box 111, Folder 2003)
    - Portraits by Carl Van Vechten at 150 West 55th Street (New York, N.Y.) (8 versions), 1932 Mar 1 (Box 111, Folder 2004)
    - Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Standing in archway with architect and foreman during construction, 1932
        See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1932, box 84, folder 1500
      - Wearing long, print dress, standing on lawn, from front, [1932] (Box 111, Folder 2005)
      - Wearing long, print dress, standing on lawn, from side, [1932]
      - Wearing long, print dress, lying in deck chair, [1932]
      - Wearing long, print dress, standing on beach, [1932]
    - Portraits by Edward Steichen
      - Sitting, from right, with eyes open, [1933]
        Inscribed by CMO to EO, 1933.
      - Sitting, from right, with eyes closed, [1933]
    - Portraits by Carl Van Vechten at Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Sitting in front of shiny curtain (11 versions), 1933 Sep 5 (Box 111, Folder 2006-2007)
      - Dressed in black, close-up (9 versions), 1933 Sep 5 (Box 112, Folder 2008)
      - Sitting in front of zig-zag background (4 versions), 1933 Oct 10 (Box 112, Folder 2009)
      - Wearing black hat and black cape (2 versions), [1933?] (Box 112, Folder 2010)
    - Wolf Lake (N.Y.)
      - Leaning against tree, [1933 or 1934] (Box 112, Folder 2011)
      - Sitting on log, [1933 or 1934]
      - Sitting on stump (2 versions), [1933 or 1934]
      - Standing next to beach, [1933 or 1934]
      - Standing on dock, [1933 or 1934]
    - Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Standing in front of wall, [1934]
      - Sitting on patio, from far away, [1935] (Box 112, Folder 2012)
      - Standing on patio steps, from far away, [1935]
      - Sitting on deck chair next to unidentified woman, [1935]
        See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1935, box 84, folder 1503
    - Portraits by Carl Van Vechten at Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Standing on garden walkway holding parasol, close-up, 1936 May 15 (Box 112, Folder 2013)
      - Standing on garden walkway holding parasol, further away, 1936 May 15
      - Standing on lawn (2 versions), 1936 May 15 (Box 112, Folder 2014)
      - Sitting outside, close-up, 1936 May (Box 112, Folder 2015)
    - Sitting, wearing plaid jacket, close-up, in Seattle (Wash.), [1936 Nov] (Box 112, Folder 2016)
    - Sitting outside on deck chair (2 versions), [193-]
      See: Green "Daily Reminder" 1937, box 85, folder 1505
    - At taping of television production of The Iceman Cometh (4 versions), 1960 (Box 112, Folder 2017)
    - Sitting reading book in front of wooden cupboard, [196-] (Box 112, Folder 2018)
  - OTHER FAMILY
    - Boulton, Agnes
      - With Shane Rudraighe O'Neill on beach in Provincetown (Mass.) (copy), [192-], n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2019)
      - With Oona Chaplin in Bermuda Islands, [192-] (Box 112, Folder 2020)
    - Chaplin, Charlie. Promotional photographs from My Autobiography (New York: Simon and Schuster, 1964)
      - "When he toured the provinces as a member of a British acting troupe" (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2021)
      - "Just before he became an international star" (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2022)
      - "With Douglas Fairbanks and Mary Pickford, during a World War I Bond selling tour" (copy) (Box 112, Folder 2023)
      - "Edward Steichen's portrait of Charles Chaplin" (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2024)
      - "Gathering of the clan for Christmas at Manoir de Ban" (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2025)
      - "A snapshot of Charles Chaplin taken by his wife, Oona O'Neill Chaplin" (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2026)
      - "In The Gold Rush " (copy), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2027)
    - Chaplin, Oona
      - Wearing costume outfit, sitting on wall in Bermuda Islands, [1927?]
      - Wearing bathing suit and cap, standing in garden at Tao House (Danville, Calif.), [1941 Jul] (Box 112, Folder 2028)
      - Swimming in pool at Tao House (Danville, Calif.) (2 versions), [1941 Jul]
      - Sitting at table outside at Tao House (Danville, Calif.) (3 versions), [1941 Jul] (Box 112, Folder 2029)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, Jr.
      - Studio portrait by Ben Pinchot, [192-] (Box 112, Folder 2030)
        Inscribed by EO, Jr. to EO.
      - Standing with double quartet singing group at Yale, [193-] (Box 112, Folder 2031)
        Annotated on back by EO, Jr.
    - O'Neill, James
      - Sitting on carved wooden chair, [186-] (Box 112, Folder 2032)
      - Standing, wearing dark suit, [18-] (Box 112, Folder 2033)
      - Portrait by Bradley & Rulofson, sitting, next to Richard M. Hooley, standing, [18--] (Box 112, Folder 2034)
        Inscribed on back by JO.
      - Standing in long coat next to table, [18--] (Box 112, Folder 2035)
      - Portrait by Sarony, N.Y., standing, wearing boots, [18--] (Box 112, Folder 2036)
      - Wearing jacket and tie, close-up, [18--] (Box 112, Folder 2037)
      - Portrait by Sarony, N.Y., standing, wearing toga, [18--] (Box 112, Folder 2038)
      - As Pierre in The Two Orphans at Union Square Theatre, N.Y., 1876 (Box 112, Folder 2039)
      - As Jesus Christ in passion play, Booth's Theatre, N.Y., 1880 Nov 22 (Box 112, Folder 2040)
        Annotated on back.
      - Portrait by Elite Photographic Studio, San Francisco (Calif.), left profile, [188-?] (Box 112, Folder 2041)
      - Portrait by Ye Rose Studio, Providence (R.I.), [18--?] (Box 112, Folder 2042)
      - Sitting with W. H. Crane in Toronto (Ont.), 1908 (Box 112, Folder 2043)
      - Portrait by John H. Ryder, Cleveland (Ohio), left profile, [191-] (Box 112, Folder 2044)
      - Portrait, from left, [191-] (Box 112, Folder 2045)
      - Standing in overcoat and hat with unidentified man, [191-] (Box 112, Folder 2046)
    - O'Neill, Mary Ellen Quinlan
      - Studio portrait, wearing bow at collar, [187-?] (Box 112, Folder 2047)
      - Studio portrait, wearing hat (copy), [187-?] (Box 112, Folder 2048)
      - Studio portrait, wearing cross (2 versions), [187-?] (Box 112, Folder 2049)
      - Empty folder (Box 112, Folder 2050)
    - O'Neill, Shane Rudraighe. At Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.)
      - Standing next to house, [1934 Dec] (Box 112, Folder 2051)
      - Sitting next to Blemie on lawn, [1934 Dec]
    - Stram, Cynthia Chapman
      - Sitting on chair outside (4 versions), with woman hidden behind chair, 1918 (Box 112, Folder 2052)
      - Studio portrait, side view, [1920?] (Box 112, Folder 2053)
      - Studio portrait, sitting with [Nellie Gotchett Tharsing?], [1920?] (Box 112, Folder 2054)
      - Outside with [Nellie Gotchett Tharsing?] in California (3 versions), [1922] (Box 112, Folder 2055)
      - Sitting on deck chair with dog on lap at Casa Genotta (Sea Island, Ga.), [1932?] (Box 112, Folder 2056)
    - Stram, Denise Dayle. Standing in living room, 1963 Dec 25 (Box 112, Folder 2057)
    - Stram, Gerald Eugene. Studio portrait, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 2058)
      In enclosure inscribed by Stram to
      CMO, 1956 Feb 4.
    - [Tharsing, Nellie Gotchett?]
      - Studio portrait by J. F. Ryder (Cleveland, Ohio) of woman, [18--?] (Box 112, Folder 2059)
        Labeled "Mother."
      - Sitting outside, [1918?] (Box 112, Folder 2060)
  - OTHER PEOPLE
    - Babb, James T.
      - Sitting in boat, holding fish, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2061)
      - Holding Long Day's Journey Into Night, standing next to unidentified man